oxfordbusinessgroup.com 2019-07-05

# Privacy Policy | | Oxford Business Group

### Data Protection Notice

This is the website of Oxford Business Group (OBG).

OBG respects the privacy of every person who visits, registers with or subscribes to our website or online publications, and is committed to ensuring a safe online experience. This Privacy Policy explains how we will collect and process your information, as well as how you can verify the accuracy of any personal information you submit through our site and how you can request that we delete or update this information.

Your privacy and security is of high importance to us and we follow the principles laid down by the European Union General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) . We only collect the personal information which you give us and we always ask you how you would like us to communicate with you. We will never sell or distribute your data to third parties without your authorisation. 

At the end of this document is a full list of all the ways in which you are able to change the details and data permissions which you have given to us.

###  What data do we collect?

We collect information which has been given to us by our registered users including all registration details (name, company, address, telephone number, email address, etc.), survey information where relevant and payment information (collected via a secure server and not retained).

For each visitor to our web pages, our web server automatically recognises the consumer's domain name. We collect only the domain name, aggregate and user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit.

We do not store customer credit card details.

###  Why do we collect your data?

We collect the data given to us by our users for the following purposes:

  1. To manage: 
    1. Report subscriptions
    2. All purchases
    3. Free trial subscriptions to our website
    4. Economic Update subscriptions  
​
  2. We use the data to manage these areas for each of the above: 
    1. Subscription start dates
    2. Subscripton end dates
    3. Renewal notices
    4. Invoicing
    5. Questions or necessary contact with regards to your orders
    6. Delivery details  
 
  3. We may also contact you to update you about OBG goods and services that we feel would be of specific interest to you and, only where permitted by you, may share your data with other selected reputable organisations which we feel would be of specific interest to you.  
 
  4. We will also disclose your data when legally required to do so at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation.  
 
  5. User data may also be aggregated (without retaining personal details) to provide us with additional insight about our customer needs and product development, and to improve the content of our website, for example by customising content for each individual visitor.  
 
  6. Finally, we use data to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against the misuse or unauthorised use of our website.

###  Data Retention policy

We securely store your information, and hold it for as long as we need to in order provide our services and products to you in accordance with (i) law, or (ii) or any relevant contract you have with us.

We also use customer purchase data for research purposes as part of our measures for improving our product and service offering.

We review our retention periods for personal information regularly. If in our audits, we find that your data no longer satisfies the conditions mentioned above, we remove them from our active database.  

###  Transferring of personal data overseas

Your personal information may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA“) and may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us, or for one of our service providers.

When we, or our permitted third parties, transfer your information outside the European Economic Area, we or they will impose contractual obligations on the recipients of that data to protect your information to the standard required in the European Economic Area. 

Some examples of when we share your information are below:

  * When you make a payment on our site, your payment will be processed by a specialist payment processor to ensure a secure transaction.
  * When we need to use delivery services to send you physical products you ordered.
  * When we send you an email or a push notification, these are delivered by marketing platforms. As part of this service, certain information such as message opens, clicks and formatting are recorded to help deliver the best email experience.
  * To provide information for auditing purposes by official regulators

###  Who is the data controller?

When you provide information to OBG, the data controller is Oxford Business Group.

###  Cookies

Please refer to our Cookies policy which can be found HERE.

###  Consent

By supplying OBG with your personal data, you consent to allow us to process your personal data for the above purposes related to your account with us or services from OBG

###  Your right to object

You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data that we carry out. The quickest way to do this is to use the unsubscribe link in any email you receive from us.

You may also do this by contact us via the methods explained at the end of this notice, or by logging into the website and changing your preferences under ‘My Details’.

Please click the 'Your Profile' link at the top of the site, followed by 'My Subscriptions', to update your Economic Update email preferences.

You can also contact us with any queries via [gdpr@oxfordbusinessgroup.com](http://www.oxfordbusinessgroup.com/)

###  Third Parties

From time to time, we may make our customer e-mail list available to other reputable organisations whose products or services we think you might find interesting.

If you do not want us to share your e-mail address, postal address or telephone number with other companies or organisations, you are able to at any time change your preferences by logging into the website and changing your preferences under the ‘My Details’ section. You can also contact us by the methods explained at the end of this notice.

###  Ad Servers

With respect to ad servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

###  Other uses

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you by email and by posting a notification in the members area.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by contacting us using the details at the end of this notice, or by updating their preferences by clicking the 'Your Profile' link at the top of the site followed by 'My Details'.

###  Updating or deleting your information

Upon request, we provide website visitors with access to all information that we maintain about them, as well as offering visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in their contact information. 

Consumers can have this information corrected by using the contact form on the Contact Us page of the website, calling us on the below telephone number, writing to us at the below address, or finally, by logging into the website and updating their details under the 'My Details' section of their profile.

If you request for us to no longer contact you via marketing communications, we will retain the minimum amount of information about you to ensure we remove you from any future communications. Please note that if you ask us to completely remove your details in our database, and you subsequently use our products and services at a later date, we won’t be able to recognise your earlier request to not be contacted, which is why we keep the minimum allowable data in order to isolate them from our send lists.

###  Security Guarantee

OBG is committed to keeping your data secure and will take appropriate measures to ensure that users’ personal data is not misused, changed, destroyed or lost within the OBG server environment.

When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site and you are at any time able to contact us via the routes below to request for changes to be made to your data, permissions or for your data to be deleted.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the below addresses or phone number, or contact the Data Protection Agency.

###  How to Contact Us

**By Post:  **  
802 Publishing Pavilion, Dubai Production City   
PO Box 502659 Me’aisem First, Dubai, UAE

**By e-mail:**  
By completing the contact form on the Contact Us page

**By telephone:   **   
+971 4 4264642

###  To change your details or permissions

You can at any time change the details we hold about you by logging into the website and updating your details under the ‘My Details’ tab of the members area. If you do not have an account, please contact us by the above methods.

If you have forgotten or do not know your password, please use your email address as your username and then follow the ‘Forgotten Password’ instructions.

###  General information about data protection may be found at:

Guide to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) | ICO: <https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/> 

General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR): <https://gdpr-info.eu/>

Direct Marketing Association (DMA) website: [http://thedma.org](https://thedma.org/)
